[
    {
        "id"                : "0",
        "question"          : "魚",
        "correct_answer"    : "さかな",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "1",
        "question"          : "肉",
        "correct_answer"    : "にく",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "2",
        "question"          : "卵",
        "correct_answer"    : "たまご",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "3",
        "question"          : "水",
        "correct_answer"    : "みず",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "4",
        "question"          : "食",
        "correct_answer"    : "た(べます)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "5",
        "question"          : "飲",
        "correct_answer"    : "の(みます)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "6",
        "question"          : "大",
        "correct_answer"    : "おお(きい)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "7",
        "question"          : "小",
        "correct_answer"    : "ちい(さい)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "8",
        "question"          : "新",
        "correct_answer"    : "あたら(しい)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "9",
        "question"          : "古",
        "correct_answer"    : "ふる(い)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "10",
        "question"          : "時",
        "correct_answer"    : "じ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "11",
        "question"          : "分",
        "correct_answer"    : "ふん・ぷん",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "12",
        "question"          : "半",
        "correct_answer"    : "はん",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "13",
        "question"          : "月",
        "correct_answer"    : "げつ(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "14",
        "question"          : "火",
        "correct_answer"    : "か(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "15",
        "question"          : "水",
        "correct_answer"    : "すい(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "16",
        "question"          : "木",
        "correct_answer"    : "もく(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "17",
        "question"          : "金",
        "correct_answer"    : "きん(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "18",
        "question"          : "土",
        "correct_answer"    : "ど(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "にち(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "19",
        "question"          : "日",
        "correct_answer"    : "にち(ようび)",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "さかな",
            "にく",
            "たまご",
            "みず",
            "た(べます)",
            "の(みます)",
            "おお(きい)",
            "ちい(さい)",
            "あたら(しい)",
            "ふる(い)",
            "じ",
            "ふん・ぷん",
            "はん",
            "げつ(ようび)",
            "か(ようび)",
            "すい(ようび)",
            "もく(ようび)",
            "きん(ようび)",
            "ど(ようび)"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "20",
        "question"          : "一",
        "correct_answer"    : "いち",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "21",
        "question"          : "二",
        "correct_answer"    : "に",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "22",
        "question"          : "三",
        "correct_answer"    : "さん",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "23",
        "question"          : "四",
        "correct_answer"    : "よん・し",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "24",
        "question"          : "五",
        "correct_answer"    : "ご",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "25",
        "question"          : "六",
        "correct_answer"    : "ろく",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "26",
        "question"          : "七",
        "correct_answer"    : "なな・しち",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "27",
        "question"          : "八",
        "correct_answer"    : "はち",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "28",
        "question"          : "九",
        "correct_answer"    : "きゅう",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "29",
        "question"          : "十",
        "correct_answer"    : "じゅう",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "30",
        "question"          : "百",
        "correct_answer"    : "ひゃく",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "せん",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "31",
        "question"          : "千",
        "correct_answer"    : "せん",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "まん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "32",
        "question"          : "万",
        "correct_answer"    : "まん",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "えん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "33",
        "question"          : "円",
        "correct_answer"    : "えん",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "いち",
            "に",
            "さん",
            "よん・し",
            "ご",
            "ろく",
            "なな・しち",
            "はち",
            "きゅう",
            "じゅう",
            "ひゃく",
            "せん",
            "まん"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "34",
        "question"          : "一つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "ひとつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ふたつ",
            "みっつ",
            "よっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "むっつ",
            "ななつ",
            "やっつ",
            "ここのつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "35",
        "question"          : "二つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "ふたつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "みっつ",
            "よっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "むっつ",
            "ななつ",
            "やっつ",
            "ここのつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "36",
        "question"          : "三つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "みっつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "ふたつ",
            "よっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "むっつ",
            "ななつ",
            "やっつ",
            "ここのつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "37",
        "question"          : "四つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "よっつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "ふたつ",
            "みっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "むっつ",
            "ななつ",
            "やっつ",
            "ここのつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "38",
        "question"          : "五つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "いつつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "ふたつ",
            "みっつ",
            "よっつ",
            "むっつ",
            "ななつ",
            "やっつ",
            "ここのつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "39",
        "question"          : "六つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "むっつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "ふたつ",
            "みっつ",
            "よっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "ななつ",
            "やっつ",
            "ここのつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "40",
        "question"          : "七つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "ななつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "ふたつ",
            "みっつ",
            "よっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "むっつ",
            "やっつ",
            "ここのつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "41",
        "question"          : "八つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "やっつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "ふたつ",
            "みっつ",
            "よっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "むっつ",
            "ななつ",
            "ここのつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "42",
        "question"          : "九つ",
        "correct_answer"    : "ここのつ",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "ふたつ",
            "みっつ",
            "よっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "むっつ",
            "ななつ",
            "やっつ",
            "とお"
        ]
    }, {
        "id"                : "43",
        "question"          : "十",
        "correct_answer"    : "とお",
        "other_answers"     : [
            "ひとつ",
            "ふたつ",
            "みっつ",
            "よっつ",
            "いつつ",
            "むっつ",
            "ななつ",
            "やっつ",
            "ここのつ"
        ]
    }
]